<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Assistive Technology on Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/tags/assistive-technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Assistive Technology on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/tags/assistive-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Information Needs of People Who Are Blind or Visually Impaired</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/information-needs-blind-low-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/information-needs-blind-low-vision/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The goal of this project is to obtain a nuanced understanding of the strategies that people who are blind or visually impaired (BVI) employ to perform different instrumental activities of daily living (iADLs).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Identifying useful and relevant visual cues that could support these iADLs, especially when the task involves some level of scene understanding, orientation, and mobility, will be essential to the success of near-future visual accessibility aids.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assistive Technologies for People Who Are Blind</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/assistive-technologies-blind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/assistive-technologies-blind/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Globally, millions of individuals with visual impairments face significant challenges in navigation and independence. Traditional white canes, while helpful, offer limited assistance in complex environments. Accessible tech, once effective, often turns commercial with hefty prices. This hits harder due to the high unemployment rate among the visually impaired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our goal is to leverage computer vision and AI to co-design the next-generation of accessible technologies with people who are blind, focusing on affordable design and open-source software, thereby enabling community-driven development and widespread impact.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
