<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/teaching/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How can we return a functional form of sight to people who are living with incurable blindness?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;d-none d-sm-block float-right col-5 m-0 ml-2&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&#34;m-0 mb-2 subtle-black-shadow&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/visual-prostheses.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&#34;mb-1&#34; style=&#34;line-height: 100%&#34;&gt;&lt;small&gt;Main approaches for the design of a visual prosthesis &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1186/s42234-018-0013-8&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Fernandez, 2018)&lt;/a&gt; include retinal (A), optic nerve (B), lateral geniculate nucleus (LGN, C), and cortical approaches (D).&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Few disabilities affect human life more than the loss of the ability to see. Although some affected individuals can be treated with surgery or medication, there are no effective treatments for many people blinded by severe degeneration or damage to the retina, the optic nerve, or cortex. In such cases, a visual prosthesis (&amp;ldquo;bionic eye&amp;rdquo;) may be the only option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the quality of current prosthetic vision is still rudimentary and does not differ much across different device technologies &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1088/1741-2552/aa795e&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Beyeler et al., 2017)&lt;/a&gt;.
A major outstanding challenge is translating electrode stimulation into a code that the brain can understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal of our research is thus to address fundamental questions at the intersection of neuroscience, computer science, and human-computer interaction that will enable the development of a bionic eye capable of restoring high-quality vision to people who are blind.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alumni</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborators</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/collaborators/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/collaborators/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grants</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/grants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/grants/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Us</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/join/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for enthusiastic, computationally minded individuals with a shared passion for bionic vision.
If you are interested in joining us, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Y1wzFVdp-FCoGM47okaW5eYdOOfpgXD5nM9Q7DpwAMo/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Lab Manual&lt;/a&gt; to familiarize yourself with our lab culture, policies, and expectations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-info-circle&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
Please note that we get a lot of emails from prospective PhD students, so Michael will not be able to respond to messages that aren&amp;rsquo;t clearly tailored to the lab&amp;rsquo;s vision.
The next deadline to join us is December 2022.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--
If you decide to &lt;a href=&#34;../people/beyeler_michael&#34;&gt;contact Michael&lt;/a&gt; before applying to the program,
you can make your application stand out by demonstrating that you have spent some time on our website, seen this message,
and thought hard about why our lab is a good fit for your skills and interest.&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Postdocs&lt;/h2&gt;
Please &lt;a href=&#34;../people/beyeler_michael&#34;&gt;contact Michael&lt;/a&gt; with your CV and a brief statement
of research accomplishments, interests, and career plans.
Although all applicants are welcome, we are especially looking for expertise at the intersection of computational neuroscience and data science. 
To be considered, you will need at least one publication 
in a high-quality international conference (computer science) 
or journal (neuroscience) 
and you need to have a reasonable chance of getting a fellowship
to support your stay at UCSB.
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;PhD Students&lt;/h3&gt;
The deadline to join us in Fall 2022 has now passed. The next deadline will happen in December 2022 (to join us in Fall 2023).
We are hiring! The next opportunity to join our lab is Fall 2022 (applications are due in December 2021).
&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-brain&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; We are looking to fill an NIH-funded PhD position in computational neuroscience. The project involves developing computational and data-driven models of the mouse visual cortex in collaboration with Spencer Smith (UCSB), Michael Goard (UCSB), and Cris Niell (U Oregon). Best to apply through DYNS. &lt;a href=&#34;../people/beyeler_michael&#34;&gt;Contact Michael&lt;/a&gt; for more info.
For all other positions, please first apply to one of the following Graduate programs:
- &lt;a href=&#34;https://cs.ucsb.edu/education/grad/admissions&#34;&gt;Department of Computer Science (CS)&lt;/a&gt;:
  Best for people interested in obtaining a formal background in 
  human-computer interaction, computer vision, and/or machine learning.
- &lt;a href=&#34;https://psych.ucsb.edu/prospective-students-0&#34;&gt;Department of Psychological &amp; Brain Sciences (PBS)&lt;/a&gt;:
  best for vision science, psychology, cognition &amp; perception
- &lt;a href=&#34;https://ece.ucsb.edu&#34;&gt;Department of Electrical &amp; Computer Engineering (ECE)&lt;/a&gt;: best for brain-inspired computing and neuromorphic engineering
- &lt;a href=&#34;https://bioengineering.ucsb.edu/academics/graduate&#34;&gt;Graduate Program in Biological Engineering (BioE)&lt;/a&gt;: best for neural engineering and computational biology
- &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dyns.ucsb.edu/graduate/admissions&#34;&gt;Graduate Program in Dynamical Neuroscience (DYNS)&lt;/a&gt;:
  best for computational neuroscience, computational vision, and brain-computer interfaces
You will then be able to indicate your wish to work with Michael in the &#34;Major and Degree Objective&#34; tab under 
&#34;Faculty Interests&#34;.
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;All Other Positions&lt;/h3&gt;
We are completely full at the moment. Please check back in March for Spring Quarter positions.
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;CS/ECE Master&#39;s Students&lt;/h3&gt;
We have several MS positions available for Fall 2021:
We are looking for students interested in applying their methodological skills to research problems in bionic vision. 
- Human-computer interaction: Build VR/AR/XR applications applied to low vision and bionic vision (Unity, compute shaders, image processing, bionic vision simulations, eye tracking)
- Biomedical image analysis: Build predictive models applied to biomedical image datasets (registration, segmentation, self-supervised learning)- 
 - Computer vision: Build predictive models applied to biomedical image datasets (registration, segmentation,
  retinal fundus imaging, optical coherence tomography). 
 - Machine learning/data science: Build predictive models applied to real-world datasets collected on retinal prosthesis
  patients (classification, regression, time-series analysis, interpretable models, heterogeneous data). 
- Neuromorphic engineering: Build brain-inspired event-based vision systems applied to scene understanding (silicon retina, spiking neural networks)
 - Software engineering/parallel programming: Develop parallelization back ends for
  &lt;a href=&#34;https://githb.com/pulse2percept/pulse2percept&#34;&gt;pulse2percept&lt;/a&gt;, our open-source Python-based simulation 
  framework (Python, Cython, SciPy, OpenMP, GPGPU, JAX).
Please &lt;a href=&#34;../people/beyeler_michael&#34;&gt;contact Michael&lt;/a&gt; to set up a time to meet.
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;Undergraduate Students&lt;/h3&gt;
We have a limited number of RA positions available for Fall 2021 (e.g., via PSY-199 or CS-196):
- Visual psychophysics: Design and run behavioral studies using VR/AR simulations of bionic vision (Unity, vision science)
- Develop applications for &lt;a href=&#34;https://githb.com/pulse2percept/pulse2percept&#34;&gt;pulse2percept&lt;/a&gt; (Python)
- Web development: Maintain and extend &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bionic-vision.org&#34;&gt;bionic-vision.org&lt;/a&gt; (React, HTML, CSS, MongoDB)
Prior research and/or programming experience is not necessary, but will drastically increase your chances of getting in
(e.g., Python/R, Matlab, Unity, web-dev).
In general, students stay for several quarters (one quarter is not enough to get up to speed)
and work for academic credit or on a volunteer basis.
Students should have a GPA of &amp;ge; 3.0 (University requirement).
If you are interested, please &lt;a href=&#34;../people/beyeler_michael&#34;&gt;contact Michael&lt;/a&gt; with your prior experience and your transcript (unofficial is fine) and we can arrange a meeting.
We are completely full. Please check back in December for Winter Quarter positions.
Typical responsibilities include one or more of the following:
- Assist in running behavioral studies (typically PSY-99 / 199)
- Develop applications for &lt;a href=&#34;https://githb.com/pulse2percept/pulse2percept&#34;&gt;pulse2percept&lt;/a&gt; (typically CS-196)
- Get hands-on research experience by shadowing a PhD student
- Process and analyze scientific data
- Perform literature reviews
- Attend weekly lab meetings and present once a quarter
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;Undergraduate Students&lt;/h3&gt;
We are looking for undergraduate students interested in assisting us with running visual psychophysics experiments in virtual reality (VR).
No prior VR/Unity experience required.
Students should have a GPA of &amp;ge; 3.0 (University requirement).
If you are interested, please &lt;a href=&#34;../people/beyeler_michael&#34;&gt;contact Michael&lt;/a&gt; with your prior experience and your transcript (unofficial is fine) and we can arrange a meeting.
--&gt;
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;Open Positions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are completely full at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/talk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
