<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/teaching/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the News</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/code/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To the best of our ability, we practice open science. The idea is not to simply tick a box of &amp;ldquo;open science&amp;rdquo;, but to make the stimuli, data, and analyses that accompany a publication readable and usable for reviewers and other researchers.
In addition, we have also developed a number of open-source software tools in support of our research goals:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How can we return a functional form of sight to people who are living with incurable blindness?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;d-none d-sm-block float-right col-5 m-0 ml-2&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img class=&#34;m-0 mb-2 subtle-black-shadow&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/visual-prostheses.jpg&#34;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&#34;mb-1&#34; style=&#34;line-height: 100%&#34;&gt;&lt;small&gt;Main approaches for the design of a visual prosthesis &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1186/s42234-018-0013-8&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Fernandez, 2018)&lt;/a&gt; include retinal (A), optic nerve (B), lateral geniculate nucleus (LGN, C), and cortical approaches (D).&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Few disabilities affect human life more than the loss of the ability to see. Although some affected individuals can be treated with surgery or medication, there are no effective treatments for many people blinded by severe degeneration or damage to the retina, the optic nerve, or cortex. In such cases, a visual prosthesis (&amp;ldquo;bionic eye&amp;rdquo;) may be the only option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the quality of current prosthetic vision is still rudimentary and does not differ much across different device technologies &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1088/1741-2552/aa795e&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;(Beyeler et al., 2017)&lt;/a&gt;.
A major outstanding challenge is translating electrode stimulation into a code that the brain can understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal of our research is thus to address fundamental questions at the intersection of neuroscience, computer science, and human-computer interaction that will enable the development of a bionic eye capable of restoring high-quality vision to people who are blind.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alumni</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborators</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/collaborators/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/collaborators/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grants</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/grants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/grants/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Us</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/join/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In general, we are looking for enthusiastic, computationally minded individuals with a shared passion for bionic vision.
If you are interested in joining us, make sure we have open positions (see below) and check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Y1wzFVdp-FCoGM47okaW5eYdOOfpgXD5nM9Q7DpwAMo/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Lab Manual&lt;/a&gt; to familiarize yourself with our lab culture, policies, and expectations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;Postdoc in Visual/Computational Neuroscience (NeuroAI)&lt;/h3&gt;
We are excited to invite a self-driven and enthusiastic postdoctoral researcher to our &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/mouse-visual-navigation/&#34;&gt;VisNav&lt;/a&gt; team.
This NeuroAI project, at the exciting crossroads of visual and computational neuroscience, is part of the NIH BRAIN Initiative that seeks to elucidate how the mouse brain processes visual information during active exploration to support visual navigation. Our recent &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/publications/2023-12-v1-mouse/&#34;&gt;NeurIPS paper&lt;/a&gt; highlights how a multimodal recurrent net can integrate gaze-contingent visual input with behavioral and temporal dynamics to explain V1 activity in freely moving mice. We are now seeking to extend this work to higher-order visual areas (HVAs) in collaboration with the labs of Spencer Smith (UCSB), Michael Goard (UCSB), and Cris Niell (University of Oregon).
What we offer:
-	A welcoming, inclusive, and collaborative environment that combines expertise in neuroscience, computer science, and cognitive sciences.
-	A fully funded, unionized position, offering a competitive salary and excellent benefits, for a minimum 2-year commitment.
-	An opportunity to work with diverse experts and engage with unique neural activity data sets, collected using state-of-the-art techniques.
We are looking for:
-	A passionate individual with a solid foundation in visual and computational neuroscience.
-	A PhD in (computational) neuroscience, computer science, cognitive sciences, statistics, or a related field
-	Strong communication and teamwork skills, with proficiency in programming and statistical analysis
To apply, please email your CV and contacts for 2-3 references to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:mbeyeler@ucsb.edu&#34;&gt;Michael&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;Junior RA Positions&lt;/h3&gt;
We are currently looking for junior research assistants (&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Y1wzFVdp-FCoGM47okaW5eYdOOfpgXD5nM9Q7DpwAMo/edit#heading=h.b7fsq3mt32v0&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Junior RAs&lt;/a&gt;). As a Junior RA, your responsibilities are three-fold:
- complete readings assigned by the lab manager/your grad student mentor; afterwards, meet with them to discuss
- attend project meetings/training sessions as your schedule allows (no need to attend lab meetings)
- participate in one or more of our ongoing behavioral studies
This is a great way to get introduced to the lab&#39;s work and the field of bionic vision.
In the future, this may lead to a Senior RA position where you can contribute more substantially to our research.
Junior RAs typically earn course credit via PSY-99/199 (P/NP or letter grade), CS-196, or your department&#39;s equivalent of Directed Research.
For more details, see our &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Y1wzFVdp-FCoGM47okaW5eYdOOfpgXD5nM9Q7DpwAMo/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;Lab Manual&lt;/a&gt;.
If you are interested in becoming a Junior RA, please reach out to our &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/people&#34;&gt;Lab Manager&lt;/a&gt;.
--&gt;
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;Undergraduate Research Positions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are completely full at the moment&lt;/strong&gt;, but you can fill out &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/XGuijmyZX9LSedwn6&#34;&gt;this form&lt;/a&gt; if you&amp;rsquo;d like to be considered for future opportunities. There is no need to further email us. You will hear from our lab manager as soon as we have space for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--
In the future, and more generally, we often accept students through the following competitive programs:
- In Computer Science (CS): &lt;a href=&#34;https://cs.ucsb.edu/education/undergraduate/special-programs&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Distinction in the Major Program (DIMAP)&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://ersp.cs.ucsb.edu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Early Research Scholars Program (ERSP)&lt;/a&gt; 
- In Psychological &amp; Brain Sciences (PBS): &lt;a href=&#34;https://psych.ucsb.edu/undergraduate/honors-program&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PBS Honors Program&lt;/a&gt;
- In the College of Engineering (CoE): &lt;a href=&#34;https://engineering.ucsb.edu/undergraduate/college-engineering-honors-program&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CoE Honors Program&lt;/a&gt;
- Across campus: &lt;a href=&#34;https://cbsr.ucsb.edu/seeds&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Student Engagement and Enrichment in Data Science (SEEDS)&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://blacksinneurocomp.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Black Researchers Advancing Neuroscience (BRAIN)&lt;/a&gt;
Summer programs:
- for high school students: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.summer.ucsb.edu/programs/research-mentorship-program/overview&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Research Mentorship Program (RMP)&lt;/a&gt;
- for undergrad students: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ucop.edu/graduate-studies/initiatives-outreach/uc-leads.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;UC Leadership Excellence through Advanced DegreeS (LEADS)&lt;/a&gt;
--&gt;
&lt;!--
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;PhD Positions for Fall 2024&lt;/h3&gt;
We have a limited number of opportunities to join us as a PhD student in Fall 2024. The deadline is December 2023.
We are especially looking for (but not limited to):
1. &lt;a href=&#34;https://cs.ucsb.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CS&lt;/a&gt;/&lt;a href=&#34;https://ece.ucsb.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ECE&lt;/a&gt;: Computer vision (CV) / human-computer interaction (HCI) students interested in &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/information-needs-blind-low-vision/&#34;&gt;assistive technologies&lt;/a&gt; and/or &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/event-based-vision/&#34;&gt;Edge AI&lt;/a&gt;. You may develop novel scene understanding algorithms, event-based CV systems, and/or prototypes of near-future accessibility aids. Your goal will be to publish at top-tier venues such as CVPR, ASSETS, or CHI.
2. &lt;a href=&#34;https://psych.ucsb.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PBS&lt;/a&gt;: Vision science students interested in working with real &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/information-needs-blind-low-vision/&#34;&gt;low vision&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/predicting-visual-outcomes-visual-prostheses/&#34;&gt;bionic eye patients&lt;/a&gt;. You may run behavioral studies and/or develop computational models to further our understanding of the neural code of vision in health and disease. You don&#39;t need a CS background for this, but should have some experience with vision/cognition, psychophysics, and/or clinical populations.
Please apply through the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.graddiv.ucsb.edu/how-apply/application-and-admission-checklist&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Grad Admissions Portal&lt;/a&gt;.
You will then be able to indicate your wish to work with us in the &#34;Major and Degree Objective&#34; tab under &#34;Faculty Interests&#34;. 
US citizens and permanent residents may apply for a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.graddiv.ucsb.edu/how-apply/faqs-applicants#Graduate-Fee&#34;&gt;fee waiver&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;small&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-info-circle&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
Please note that we get a lot of emails from prospective PhD students, so Michael will not be able to respond to messages that aren&#39;t clearly tailored to the lab&#39;s vision, especially if it is apparent that the same &#34;boilerplate&#34; message is being sent to many different labs.
You can make your application stand out by demonstrating that you have spent time on our website, &lt;i&gt;seen this message&lt;/i&gt;, and thought hard about why our lab is a good fit for your skills and interests.&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;All Other Positions&lt;/h3&gt;
We are completely full. Undergraduate students, please check back in January 2024 for Winter Quarter positions.
&lt;h2&gt;Postdocs&lt;/h2&gt;
Please &lt;a href=&#34;../people/beyeler_michael&#34;&gt;contact Michael&lt;/a&gt; with your CV and a brief statement
of research accomplishments, interests, and career plans.
Although all applicants are welcome, we are especially looking for expertise at the intersection of computational neuroscience and data science. 
To be considered, you will need at least one publication 
in a high-quality international conference (computer science) 
or journal (neuroscience) 
and you need to have a reasonable chance of getting a fellowship
to support your stay at UCSB.
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;CS/ECE Master&#39;s Students&lt;/h3&gt;
We have several MS positions available for Fall 2021:
We are looking for students interested in applying their methodological skills to research problems in bionic vision. 
- Human-computer interaction: Build VR/AR/XR applications applied to low vision and bionic vision (Unity, compute shaders, image processing, bionic vision simulations, eye tracking)
- Biomedical image analysis: Build predictive models applied to biomedical image datasets (registration, segmentation, self-supervised learning)- 
 - Computer vision: Build predictive models applied to biomedical image datasets (registration, segmentation,
  retinal fundus imaging, optical coherence tomography). 
 - Machine learning/data science: Build predictive models applied to real-world datasets collected on retinal prosthesis
  patients (classification, regression, time-series analysis, interpretable models, heterogeneous data). 
- Neuromorphic engineering: Build brain-inspired event-based vision systems applied to scene understanding (silicon retina, spiking neural networks)
 - Software engineering/parallel programming: Develop parallelization back ends for
  &lt;a href=&#34;https://githb.com/pulse2percept/pulse2percept&#34;&gt;pulse2percept&lt;/a&gt;, our open-source Python-based simulation 
  framework (Python, Cython, SciPy, OpenMP, GPGPU, JAX).
Please &lt;a href=&#34;../people/beyeler_michael&#34;&gt;contact Michael&lt;/a&gt; to set up a time to meet.
Typical responsibilities include one or more of the following:
- Assist in running behavioral studies (typically PSY-99 / 199)
- Develop applications for &lt;a href=&#34;https://githb.com/pulse2percept/pulse2percept&#34;&gt;pulse2percept&lt;/a&gt; (typically CS-196)
- Get hands-on research experience by shadowing a PhD student
- Process and analyze scientific data
- Perform literature reviews
- Attend weekly lab meetings and present once a quarter
&lt;h3 class=&#34;fill-width&#34;&gt;Undergraduate Students&lt;/h3&gt;
In addition, we often accept students through the following competitive programs:
- In Computer Science (CS): &lt;a href=&#34;https://cs.ucsb.edu/education/undergraduate/special-programs&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Distinction in the Major Program (DIMAP)&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://ersp.cs.ucsb.edu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Early Research Scholars Program (ERSP)&lt;/a&gt; 
- In Psychological &amp; Brain Sciences (PBS): &lt;a href=&#34;https://psych.ucsb.edu/undergraduate/honors-program&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PBS Honors Program&lt;/a&gt;
- In the College of Engineering (CoE): &lt;a href=&#34;https://engineering.ucsb.edu/undergraduate/college-engineering-honors-program&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CoE Honors Program&lt;/a&gt;
- Across campus: &lt;a href=&#34;https://cbsr.ucsb.edu/seeds&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Student Engagement and Enrichment in Data Science (SEEDS)&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://blacksinneurocomp.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Black Researchers Advancing Neuroscience (BRAIN)&lt;/a&gt;
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;gallery2 caption-position-none caption-effect-slide hover-effect-zoom hover-transition&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageGallery&#34;&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//001%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20and%20the%20ERSP%20Team%20standing%20in%20front%20of%20their%20research%20poster.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//001%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20and%20the%20ERSP%20Team%20standing%20in%20front%20of%20their%20research%20poster.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;001 prof&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;001 prof&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//001%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20and%20the%20ERSP%20Team%20standing%20in%20front%20of%20their%20research%20poster.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;001 prof&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//002%20Byron%20Johnson%20presenting%20at%20VSS.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//002%20Byron%20Johnson%20presenting%20at%20VSS.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;002 byron johnson presenting at vss&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;002 byron johnson presenting at vss&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//002%20Byron%20Johnson%20presenting%20at%20VSS.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;002 byron johnson presenting at vss&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//003%20Argus%20II%20user%20drawing%20a%20perceived%20phosphene%20on%20a%20touchscreen%20in%20front%20of%20him.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//003%20Argus%20II%20user%20drawing%20a%20perceived%20phosphene%20on%20a%20touchscreen%20in%20front%20of%20him.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;003 argus ii user drawing a perceived phosphene on a touchscreen in front of him&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;003 argus ii user drawing a perceived phosphene on a touchscreen in front of him&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//003%20Argus%20II%20user%20drawing%20a%20perceived%20phosphene%20on%20a%20touchscreen%20in%20front%20of%20him.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;003 argus ii user drawing a perceived phosphene on a touchscreen in front of him&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//004%20Group%20picture%20of%20the%20BVL%20team%20at%20The%20Eye%20and%20The%20Chip%202023.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//004%20Group%20picture%20of%20the%20BVL%20team%20at%20The%20Eye%20and%20The%20Chip%202023.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;004 group picture of the bvl team at the eye and the chip 2023&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;004 group picture of the bvl team at the eye and the chip 2023&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//004%20Group%20picture%20of%20the%20BVL%20team%20at%20The%20Eye%20and%20The%20Chip%202023.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;004 group picture of the bvl team at the eye and the chip 2023&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//005%20Dr%20Justin%20Kasowski%20getting%20hooded%20at%20the%202023%20Commencement%20Ceremony.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//005%20Dr%20Justin%20Kasowski%20getting%20hooded%20at%20the%202023%20Commencement%20Ceremony.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;005 dr justin kasowski getting hooded at the 2023 commencement ceremony&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;005 dr justin kasowski getting hooded at the 2023 commencement ceremony&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//005%20Dr%20Justin%20Kasowski%20getting%20hooded%20at%20the%202023%20Commencement%20Ceremony.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;005 dr justin kasowski getting hooded at the 2023 commencement ceremony&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//006%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20and%20students%20with%20Orion%20implant%20recipient%20Jason%20Esterhuizen.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//006%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20and%20students%20with%20Orion%20implant%20recipient%20Jason%20Esterhuizen.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;006 prof&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;006 prof&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//006%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20and%20students%20with%20Orion%20implant%20recipient%20Jason%20Esterhuizen.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;006 prof&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//007%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20sitting%20on%20a%20panel%20with%20prosthesis%20experts%20at%20the%20Eye%20and%20the%20Chip%202023.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//007%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20sitting%20on%20a%20panel%20with%20prosthesis%20experts%20at%20the%20Eye%20and%20the%20Chip%202023.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;007 prof&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;007 prof&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//007%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20sitting%20on%20a%20panel%20with%20prosthesis%20experts%20at%20the%20Eye%20and%20the%20Chip%202023.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;007 prof&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//008%20Blind%20participant%20using%20a%20smartphone%20app%20to%20read%20the%20label%20on%20a%20jar%20of%20Mayonnaise.png&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//008%20Blind%20participant%20using%20a%20smartphone%20app%20to%20read%20the%20label%20on%20a%20jar%20of%20Mayonnaise.png&#34; alt=&#34;008 blind participant using a smartphone app to read the label on a jar of mayonnaise&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;008 blind participant using a smartphone app to read the label on a jar of mayonnaise&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//008%20Blind%20participant%20using%20a%20smartphone%20app%20to%20read%20the%20label%20on%20a%20jar%20of%20Mayonnaise.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;008 blind participant using a smartphone app to read the label on a jar of mayonnaise&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//009%20Jacob%20Granley%20in%20front%20of%20his%20poster%20at%20NeurIPS%202022.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//009%20Jacob%20Granley%20in%20front%20of%20his%20poster%20at%20NeurIPS%202022.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;009 jacob granley in front of his poster at neur IP s 2022&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;009 jacob granley in front of his poster at neur IP s 2022&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//009%20Jacob%20Granley%20in%20front%20of%20his%20poster%20at%20NeurIPS%202022.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;009 jacob granley in front of his poster at neur IP s 2022&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//010%20Justin%20Kasowski%20presenting%20his%20work%20on%20SimpleXR%20at%20VSS%202023.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//010%20Justin%20Kasowski%20presenting%20his%20work%20on%20SimpleXR%20at%20VSS%202023.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;010 justin kasowski presenting his work on simple xr at vss 2023&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;010 justin kasowski presenting his work on simple xr at vss 2023&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//010%20Justin%20Kasowski%20presenting%20his%20work%20on%20SimpleXR%20at%20VSS%202023.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;010 justin kasowski presenting his work on simple xr at vss 2023&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//011%20Galen%20Pogoncheff%20using%20the%20Bionic%20Vision%20XR%20Simulator.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//011%20Galen%20Pogoncheff%20using%20the%20Bionic%20Vision%20XR%20Simulator.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;011 galen pogoncheff using the bionic vision xr simulator&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;011 galen pogoncheff using the bionic vision xr simulator&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//011%20Galen%20Pogoncheff%20using%20the%20Bionic%20Vision%20XR%20Simulator.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;011 galen pogoncheff using the bionic vision xr simulator&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//012%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20demoing%20BionicVisionXR%20at%20VSS%202023%20while%20a%20participant%20is%20using%20the%20head-mounted%20display.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//012%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20demoing%20BionicVisionXR%20at%20VSS%202023%20while%20a%20participant%20is%20using%20the%20head-mounted%20display.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;012 prof&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;012 prof&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//012%20Prof.%20Beyeler%20demoing%20BionicVisionXR%20at%20VSS%202023%20while%20a%20participant%20is%20using%20the%20head-mounted%20display.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;012 prof&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//013%20Mac%20and%20Cheese%20trophy%20given%20to%20first%20place%20winner%20Lily%20Turkstra%20at%20the%20lab%27s%20first%20competitive%20Mac%20and%20Cheese%20cookoff.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//013%20Mac%20and%20Cheese%20trophy%20given%20to%20first%20place%20winner%20Lily%20Turkstra%20at%20the%20lab%27s%20first%20competitive%20Mac%20and%20Cheese%20cookoff.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;013 MAC and cheese trophy given to first place winner lily turkstra at the lab&amp;#39;s first competitive MAC and cheese cookoff&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;013 MAC and cheese trophy given to first place winner lily turkstra at the lab&amp;#39;s first competitive MAC and cheese cookoff&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//013%20Mac%20and%20Cheese%20trophy%20given%20to%20first%20place%20winner%20Lily%20Turkstra%20at%20the%20lab%27s%20first%20competitive%20Mac%20and%20Cheese%20cookoff.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;013 MAC and cheese trophy given to first place winner lily turkstra at the lab&amp;#39;s first competitive MAC and cheese cookoff&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//014%20Group%20picture%20of%20the%20BVL%20team%20at%20the%20Mac%20and%20Cheese%20cookoff.jpg&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//014%20Group%20picture%20of%20the%20BVL%20team%20at%20the%20Mac%20and%20Cheese%20cookoff.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;014 group picture of the bvl team at the MAC and cheese cookoff&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;014 group picture of the bvl team at the MAC and cheese cookoff&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//014%20Group%20picture%20of%20the%20BVL%20team%20at%20the%20Mac%20and%20Cheese%20cookoff.jpg&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;014 group picture of the bvl team at the MAC and cheese cookoff&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//015%20BVL%20team%20members%20enjoying%20a%20cake%20to%20celebrate%20their%20successful%20NeurIPS%20submissions.png&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//015%20BVL%20team%20members%20enjoying%20a%20cake%20to%20celebrate%20their%20successful%20NeurIPS%20submissions.png&#34; alt=&#34;015 bvl team members enjoying a cake to celebrate their successful neur IP s submissions&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;015 bvl team members enjoying a cake to celebrate their successful neur IP s submissions&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/img/gallery//015%20BVL%20team%20members%20enjoying%20a%20cake%20to%20celebrate%20their%20successful%20NeurIPS%20submissions.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34; alt=&#34;015 bvl team members enjoying a cake to celebrate their successful neur IP s submissions&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
 



  





&lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/photoswipe/4.1.1/photoswipe.min.css&#34; integrity=&#34;sha256-sCl5PUOGMLfFYctzDW3MtRib0ctyUvI9Qsmq2wXOeBY=&#34; crossorigin=&#34;anonymous&#34; /&gt;
&lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/photoswipe/4.1.1/default-skin/default-skin.min.css&#34; integrity=&#34;sha256-BFeI1V+Vh1Rk37wswuOYn5lsTcaU96hGaI7OUVCLjPc=&#34; crossorigin=&#34;anonymous&#34; /&gt;



&lt;div class=&#34;pswp&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34; role=&#34;dialog&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;pswp__bg&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;pswp__scroll-wrap&#34;&gt;
    
    &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__container&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__item&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__item&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__item&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
    &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__ui pswp__ui--hidden&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__top-bar&#34;&gt;
      
      &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__counter&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--close&#34; title=&#34;Close (Esc)&#34;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
      &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--share&#34; title=&#34;Share&#34;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
      &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--fs&#34; title=&#34;Toggle fullscreen&#34;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
      &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--zoom&#34; title=&#34;Zoom in/out&#34;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
      
      
      &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__preloader&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__preloader__icn&#34;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__preloader__cut&#34;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__preloader__donut&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__share-modal pswp__share-modal--hidden pswp__single-tap&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__share-tooltip&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--arrow--left&#34; title=&#34;Previous (arrow left)&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--arrow--right&#34; title=&#34;Next (arrow right)&#34;&gt;
    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__caption&#34;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__caption__center&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/talk/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
