<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code on Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Code on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BionicVisionXR: An Open-Source Virtual Reality Toolbox for Bionic Vision</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/code/bionicvisionxr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/code/bionicvisionxr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A major outstanding challenge in the field of bionic vision is predicting what people “see” when they use their devices.
The limited field of view of current devices necessitates head movements to scan the scene, which is difficult to simulate on a computer screen. 
In addition, many computational models of bionic vision lack biological realism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To address these challenges, we present &lt;em&gt;BionicVisionXR&lt;/em&gt;, an open-source virtual reality toolbox for simulated prosthetic vision that uses a psychophysically validated computational model to allow sighted participants to “see through the eyes” of a bionic
eye user.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pulse2percept: A Python-Based Simulation Framework for Bionic Vision</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/code/pulse2percept/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/code/pulse2percept/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;pulse2percept&lt;/em&gt; is a BSD-licensed, open-source Python package for simulated prosthetic vision (SPV).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built on the NumPy and SciPy stacks, as well as contributions from the broader Python community, &lt;em&gt;pulse2percept&lt;/em&gt; provides an open-source implementation of several phosphene models for a wide range of state-of-the-art retinal prostheses, to provide insight into the visual experience provided by these devices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As &lt;em&gt;pulse2percept&lt;/em&gt; continues to be adopted by several research labs around the globe, we continue to improve its functionality and performance as well as add new implants, models, and datasets.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
