<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>In the News on Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in In the News on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 09:29:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A neural autoencoder to enhance sensory neuroprostheses</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2022-06-techxplore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 09:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2022-06-techxplore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What is the required stimulus to produce a desired percept?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our latest work on deep learning-based stimulus optimization was featured in a news article by TechXplore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We started working on this project in an attempt to solve the long-standing problem of stimulus optimization in visual prostheses,&amp;rdquo; &lt;a href=&#34;https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/granley_jacob&#34;&gt;Jacob Granley&lt;/a&gt;, one of the researchers who carried out the study, told TechXplore. &amp;ldquo;One of the likely causes for the poor results achieved by visual prostheses is the naive stimulus encoding strategy that devices conventionally use. Previous works have suggested encoding strategies, but many are unrealistic, and none have given a general solution that could work across implants and patients.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the full article at &lt;a href=&#34;https://techxplore.com/news/2022-06-neural-autoencoder-sensory-neuroprostheses.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will it ever be possible to upload information to my brain?</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2021-09-giz-asks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2021-09-giz-asks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Prof. Beyeler was part of the Giz Asks series, where the focused turned to the prospect of using brain-machine interface technology to directly write in information to the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the full interview &lt;a href=&#34;https://gizmodo.com/will-it-be-possible-to-upload-information-to-my-brain-1847698784&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCMag: Building the bionic eye... with car tech?</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2021-02-pcmag/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 09:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2021-02-pcmag/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the years, cyberpunk tales and sci-fi series have featured characters with cybernetic vision—most recently Star Trek Discovery&amp;rsquo;s Lieutenant Keyla Detmer and her ocular implants. In the real world, restoring “natural” vision is still a complex puzzle, though researchers at UC Santa Barbara are developing a smart prosthesis that provides cues to the visually impaired, much like a computer vision system talks to a self-driving car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, over 10 million people worldwide are living with profound visual impairment, many due to retinal degeneration diseases. Ahead of this week&amp;rsquo;s Augmented Humans International Conference, we spoke with Dr. Michael Beyeler, Assistant Professor in Computer Science and Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences at UCSB, who is forging ahead with synthetic sight trials at his Bionic Vision Lab and will be presenting a paper at the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the full interview &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pcmag.com/news/building-the-bionic-eyewith-car-tech&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SciSection: Interview with Michael Beyeler</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2020-10-scisection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 09:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2020-10-scisection/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Beyeler sat down with Luming Cao from SciSection&amp;rsquo;s Human and Science platform to talk about how bionic vision, as sci-fi as it sounds, is already helping to restore vision to the blind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The transcript of this informal interview is now available, and a podcast will follow soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the full interview &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.humansandscience.com/post/interview-with-dr-beyeler&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCSB Convergence: Reverse engineering the brain</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2020-05-convergence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 09:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2020-05-convergence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Michael Beyeler and the Bionic Vision Lab are featured heavily in the Spring Edition of UCSB&amp;rsquo;s College of Engineering Convergence Magazine:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;There is research to try to understand the brain—how it works on a mechanistic and algorithmic level—and then there&amp;rsquo;s applying that to an engineered system that can interface with the brain,&amp;rdquo; says Michael Beyeler, an assistant professor in Computer Science and Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences, in providing context for his research, which lies in the emerging interdisciplinary field of neuroengineering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Brain-computer interfaces can be used both for treating neurological and mental disorders as well as for understanding brain function,” he says. “Eventually, they should also allow us to restore vision to the blind.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the full article &lt;a href=&#34;https://engineering.ucsb.edu/convergence/spring-2020&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCMag: Restoring vision with bionic eyes - no longer science fiction</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2019-07-pcmag/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 09:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/news/2019-07-pcmag/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new article appeared in PCMag to celebrate the inauguration of the Bionic Vision Lab at UCSB:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bionic vision might sound like science fiction, but Dr. Michael Beyeler is working on just that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Originally from Switzerland, Dr. Beyeler is wrapping up his postdoctoral fellow at the University of Washington before moving to the University of California Santa Barbara this fall to head up the newly formed Bionic Vision Lab in the Departments of Computer Science and Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We spoke with him about this &amp;ldquo;deep fascination with the brain&amp;rdquo; and how he hopes his work will eventually be able to restore vision to the blind. Here are edited and condensed excerpts from our conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the full article &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pcmag.com/news/369401/restoring-vision-with-bionic-eyes-no-longer-science-fiction&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
