<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alumni on Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alumni on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/adimulam_kartik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/adimulam_kartik/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kartik Adimulam is a 3rd-year undergraduate Statistics &amp;amp; Data Science major at UC Santa Barbara. He is fascinated by the use of artificial intelligence and computational neuroscience to solve modern-day health issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he is not learning about data science or pursuing his interests as a researcher, he enjoys watching podcasts and playing basketball with his fraternity. He also enjoys working on supplementary personal data science projects focused on algorithmic trading.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/afshari_kimia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/afshari_kimia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kimia Afshari is a MS Student in Computer Science and a member of the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/akkaraju_anvitha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/akkaraju_anvitha/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anvitha Akkaraju is an undergraduate student in the Department of Psychological and Brain Sciences at the University of California, Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/aluru_sriya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/aluru_sriya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sriya Aluru is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara, and a scholar in the Early Research Scholars Program (ERSP). She is interested in Deep Learning and Computational Neuroscience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She loves hanging out at the beach, trying new places to eat, and playing tennis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/arenberg_nick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/arenberg_nick/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nick Arenberg is currently a fourth-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. He is working on improving pulse2percept with new features an optimizations and is interested in scientific computing and software engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he is not coding, he enjoys playing ice hockey on the UCSB club team, going to concerts, and cooking.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/bhatia_tanya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/bhatia_tanya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tanya Bhatia is an undergraduate research assistant pursuing a degree in biopsychology. She is interested in better understanding and improving the perceptual experience of sight recovery patients and the clinical applications of computational neuroscience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/bodolay_alec/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/bodolay_alec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alec Bodolay is currently a fourth-year undergraduate student pursuing a Biopsychology degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/bruce_ashley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/bruce_ashley/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ashley is currently a Master&amp;rsquo;s Student in the Computer Science Department at UC Santa Barbara. She graduated with her Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s in Biology at Cal Poly San Luis Obispo in 2019 and her Associate&amp;rsquo;s in Computer Science at Cuesta College in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/brydon_annika/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/brydon_annika/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Annika Brydon is currently a first-year undergraduate student pursuing an Environmental Studies degree at UC Santa Barbara. She is working on developing questions to understand how low vision impacts quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she is not developing research questions, she enjoys walking on the beach and baking delicious treats.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/chan_cheng/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/chan_cheng/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cheng Han (Johnson) Chan is a BS student in the Department of Computer Science.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/chau_alexander/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/chau_alexander/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alexander Chau is currently a first-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/chung_justin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/chung_justin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Justin Chung is a BS student in the Department of Computer Science.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/eckhardt_lauren/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/eckhardt_lauren/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lauren Eckhardt is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Biopsychology degree at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in neuroprosthetics and computational neuroscience.
In her free time, she enjoys hiking, camping and reading.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/gangaswamy_harshita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/gangaswamy_harshita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Harshita Gangaswamy is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Engineering degree at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in deep learning and computational neuroscience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she is not studying and doing research, she enjoys reading novels and watching TV shows with her roommates and friends. She has also been volunteering to teach kids through the Society of Women Engineers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/gao_emma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/gao_emma/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/gao_ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/gao_ethan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ethan Gao is a rising senior high school student at Ojai Valley School and will graduate in 2021. He has joined the lab as an RMP (Research Mentorship Program) student and brings a love of computer science and a curiosity about advanced programming techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At School, he is heavily involved in computer science and math, being the team captain and programmer of the competitive robotics team and member of the competitive Math team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the Bionic Vision Lab, Ethan is helping develop a virtual reality model of retinal prosthesis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/garg_umang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/garg_umang/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Umang is a graduate student pursuing Integrated MS-PhD program in the ECE Department at UCSB. He is primarily interested in machine learning, vision systems, and computationally efficient brain-inspired algorithms. He is passionate about employing these algorithms to design fast and robust edge-vision systems dedicated to tasks like object recognition and tracking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Off work, you can generally find him hiking on weekends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/gee_robert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/gee_robert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Robert Gee is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/giduthuri_anand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/giduthuri_anand/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anand Giduthuri is currently a second-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. His interests include computer vision and deep learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his free time, he likes to spend time at the beach and play badminton.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/ho_elaine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/ho_elaine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Elaine Ho is currently a first-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/hou_yuchen2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/hou_yuchen2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yuchen Hou&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/htun_chitsein/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/htun_chitsein/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/hu_zuying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/hu_zuying/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Zuying Hu is an MS student at UC Santa Barbara and member of the Bionic Vision Lab. His interests lie in computer vision and machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He received his higher education in Guangzhou and Hong Kong. He received his BS in Information Engineering from the Chinese University of Hong Kong in 2017 and his MS in Big Data Technology at Hong Kong University of Science and Technology in 2018. With a passion for machine learning and computer vision, he decided to continue his study at UCSB and looks forward to applying his knowledge in daily use.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/iyer_nandini/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/iyer_nandini/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nandini Iyer is currently a second-year undergraduate student pursuing degrees in Economics and Statistics &amp;amp; Data Science at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in machine learning and computational neuroscience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she is not drowning in schoolwork, she enjoys playing volleyball and watching soccer. She has also been working alongside the Economics Department DEI Committee.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/jain_yash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/jain_yash/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/jasper_surya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/jasper_surya/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/jha_rutvik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/jha_rutvik/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rutvik Jha is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Engineering degree at UC Santa Barbara. He is working on event-based deep learning models and is interested in deploying cutting-edge deep learning techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/johnson_wayne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/johnson_wayne/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wayne Johnson is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences degree at UC Santa Barbara. He is working on how people&amp;rsquo;s perceptions change when encountered with first or second hand information from society and is interested in going to graduate school for psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he is not doing major university stuff, he enjoys having fun making music, reading, sports and his favorite food is Italian. He has also been volunteering with the democratic grassroots foundation canvassing / phone banking and making donations to his old community college.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/kasowski_justin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/kasowski_justin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Justin Kasowksi transferred to UC Santa Barbara in 2016 after receiving associates degrees in Biological Sciences and Chemistry from Santa Barbara City College. In 2018, he graduated UCSB with a degree in Molecular, Cellular, and Developmental Biology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is pursuing his PhD under Dr. Michael Beyeler in the Bionic Vision Lab, where he utilizes virtual reality and computer vision to model the perceptual experience of retinal prosthesis patients.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/khachatryan_mari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/khachatryan_mari/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mari Khachatryan is an undergraduate student pursuing a Biopsychology degree at UC Santa Barbara. 
She is interested in visual neuroscience especially the neural networks behind eye surgeries such as LASIK, Photorefractive keratectomy, and lens replacement surgery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Mari likes to jog to Sands beach, try out new restaurants, and hang out with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/kolhatkar_rucha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/kolhatkar_rucha/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/levier_tori/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/levier_tori/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tori LeVier&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/li_lisa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/li_lisa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/liang_andrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/liang_andrew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Andrew Liang is a high schooler at The Harker School in San Jose, California. He is interested in using machine learning to help the blind navigate. His other interests include playing chess and competitive programming.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/lin_dylan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/lin_dylan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dylan Lin is a third-year undergraduate student in the department of Computer Science at the University of California, Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/mahes_ananth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/mahes_ananth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ananth Mahes is an undergraduate student pursuing a degree in Biopsychology at the University of California, Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/makineni_meghana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/makineni_meghana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Meghana Makineni is a fourth year student pursuing a BS in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in computational neuroscience, vision science, and biomedical engineering, and is part of the content team at the Bionic Vision Lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time she enjoys yoga, writing, listening to music, and going to the beach with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/mao_andre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/mao_andre/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/meade_ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/meade_ethan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ethan Meade is a BS student in the Department of Computer Science. He is interested in doing work at the intersection of machine learning and human-computer interaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ethan is a Regents Scholar and Honors Student in the Distinction in the Major Program (DIMAP) of the CS department.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/mihlar_khalid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/mihlar_khalid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Khalid Mihlar is a BS student pursuing a Computer Engineering degree along with a Certificate in Technology Management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has previously worked at a startup known as AVIAI and The Boeing Company. He is interested in biomedical research with a focus on neuroscience with the goal to find more opportunities in his future within this field.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/mizrahi_ori/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/mizrahi_ori/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ori Mizrahi is a fourth-year undergraduate student studying Computer Science at the University of California, Santa Barbara. He is interested in applying computational science to the development and advancement of useful sight restoration technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/mochizuki_rachel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/mochizuki_rachel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rachel Mochizuki is currently a fourth-year undergraduate student pursuing a Biopsychology degree at UC Santa Barbara.
She joined the lab in January 2021 to conduct her senior honors thesis.
Her research will focus on how the severity of visual impairment affects quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/naik_sahil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/naik_sahil/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sahil Naik is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Engineering degree at UC Santa Barbara. He is currently interested in Computational Neuroscience and Artificial Intelligence but hopes to delve more into deep learning in the future.
He also really loves the beach and beach games like die and spikeball.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/neydavood_ryan2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/neydavood_ryan2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ryan Neydavood&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/neydavood_ryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/neydavood_ryan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ryan Neydavood is a staff scientist, research coordinator, and lab manager of the Bionic Vision Lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He graduated from UC Santa Barbara in 2021 with a degree in Psychology &amp;amp; Brain Sciences. He was born and raised in Los Angeles, California where he developed a commitment to healthcare. Ryan is interested in Virtual Reality, neurophysiology, and advancing the field of bionic vision to help cure blindness.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/nguyen_bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/nguyen_bill/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bill Nguyen is an undergraduate student in the Departments of Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences (PBS) and Mathematics at UC Santa Barbara. He is interested in the exciting potential of neural prostheses, both on a technological and clinical level.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/nguyen_kha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/nguyen_kha/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kha Nguyen is an upcoming third-year transfer student in the Department of Bioengineering at the University of California, San Diego.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the UC Leadership Excellence through Advanced DegreeS (UC LEADS) program, she is working with the Bionic Vision Lab to evaluate and improve existing phosphene models for retinal implants.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/novick_julia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/novick_julia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Julia Novick is currently a first-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree in the College of Creative Studies at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in software engineering and reverse-engineering the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/olmos_ruben/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/olmos_ruben/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ruben Olmos is a research assistant and computer programmer in the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara (UCSB).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is completing his undergraduate education in Statistics and Data Science (B.S) at UCSB. Prior to joining the Bionic Vision Lab, he worked as part of the UCSB Baseball Data Analytics organization conducting application based statistical research, modeling &amp;amp; analysis and developing data intensive software programs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/ondo_megumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/ondo_megumi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Megumi Ondo is an undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/pullela_laya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/pullela_laya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Laya Pullela is a BS Student in the College of Creative Studies and a member of the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara.
She is interested in applying machine learning and computational biology to medical applications.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/qi_ziming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/qi_ziming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ziming Qi is a MS student at UC Santa Barbara and member of the Bionic Vision Lab. He is interested in computer vision and machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He received his BS degree in computer engineering at UCSB, and is currently pursuing his MS degree at UCSB as well. With passion to save people&amp;rsquo;s vision, he decided to apply his computer vision and machine learning skills in the area of biomedical image analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/raghulan_rashi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/raghulan_rashi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rashi Raghulan is an undergraduate student in the Department of Molecular, Cellular, and Development Biology at the University of California, Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/rasla_alex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/rasla_alex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alex Rasla is currently a first-year graduate student in the B.S/M.S. program pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. He is interested in Machine Learning, Computer Vision, AR/VR, and autonomous systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his free time, Alex enjoys playing the piano or guitar, and producing music. Some of his other hobbies include hanging out at the beach, reading books, and playing sports. Once he graduates, Alex wants to work for a company that makes the world a better place.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/relic_lucas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/relic_lucas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lucas Relic is currently a Master&amp;rsquo;s Student in the Computer Science Department at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/rohatgi_versha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/rohatgi_versha/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Versha Rohatgi is a rising junior at Mountain View High School and is part of the Research Mentorship Program at UC Santa Barbara. Versha is interested in biomedical engineering and computer science.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/roma_ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/roma_ethan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ethan Roma is currently a fourth-year undergraduate student pursuing a Biopsychology degree in the College of Letters and Science at UC Santa Barbara. He wants to learn more about the behavioral and physiological causes of losses in sensation such as sight, and how technical prosthetics might be enabled/designed to address said losses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his free time, he enjoys making music, skateboarding, and late night drive-thrus with his friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/salgado_zavaleta_vanessa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/salgado_zavaleta_vanessa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Vanessa Salgado is currently a fourth-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested Data Science, Deep Learning, and Neural Networks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, she loves rock climbing and spending time outdoors with her friends. Her hobbies include reading memoirs, trying new restaurants, and discovering new music. After graduation, Vanessa would like to use technology for social good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/sama_shivani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/sama_shivani/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shivani Sama is a student at Tesla STEM High School in Redmond, WA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She is participating in the Central Sound Regional Science and Engineering Fair at Bellevue College, to be held in March 2023. 
For this project she is interested in researching brain computer interfaces (specifically deep brain stimulation) and how they can be used to induce neuroplasticity and neuron regrowth to treat various types of neurodegenerative diseases and paralysis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/sanchez_garcia_melani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/sanchez_garcia_melani/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Melani Sanchez Garica is a Postdoctoral Researcher in the Department of Computer Science at UCSB.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining UCSB, she received a PhD in Computer Science and Systems Engineering from Universidad de Zaragoza, Spain, as well as a BS in Chemical Engineering and a MS in Chemical Engineering from Universidad de Valencia, Spain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Melani&amp;rsquo;s main research interests lie in Computer Vision and Deep Learning. She is particularly excited about conducting research in simulated prosthetic vision (SPV) and building immersive virtual reality (VR) systems of SPV that combine computational modeling of the brain with different computer vision algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/shen_emma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/shen_emma/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emma Shen is currently a rising senior at Del Norte High School in San Diego, CA. She is interested in exploring the multidisciplinary nature of Computer Science, particularly human-computer interactions and computational neuroscience. In her free time, she enjoys playing tennis, reading dystopian realistic fiction novels, and taking long strolls in picturesque landscapes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/sista_shivani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/sista_shivani/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shivani Sista is currently a second-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara, and a scholar in the Early Research Scholars Program (ERSP). She is interested in deep learning, computer vision, and computational neuroscience. In her free time, she enjoys playing the violin, drawing, and watching TV.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/solares_angel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/solares_angel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Angel Solares is a senior in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences at UC Santa Barbara. He is interested in getting his foot in the door of research in nueropsychology and related fields. He worked as a behavioral technician before transferring to UCSB, and is a Packers fan through and through.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/spiker_madori/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/spiker_madori/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Madori Spiker is a MS student in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/su_jiaxin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/su_jiaxin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jiaxin Su is an undergraduate student pursuing degrees in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences as well as in Data Science and Statistics at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She is interested in working at the intersection of biostatistics and psychology. In her free time, she enjoys running and playing frisbee.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/supramaniam_gita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/supramaniam_gita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gita Supramaniam is currently a second-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, she enjoys reading and going on walks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/tang_molly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/tang_molly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Molly Tang is currently a fourth year undergraduate pursing a degree in Biological Sciences at UC Santa Barbara and a member of the Promise Scholars Program. She is interested in new opportunities, particularly in computational biology with a focus in biomedical research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, she enjoys playing video games, occasional weight lifting, and spending time with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/tang_shuyun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/tang_shuyun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shuyun Tang is an undergraduate research assistant in the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is a fourth-year undergraduate student in Statistics and Data Science at UCSB. In the Bionic Vision Lab, he works with Ziming Qi in biomedical image analysis projects that seeking to save people’s vision.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/tanna_avani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/tanna_avani/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Avani Tanna is currently a MS student in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/tapia_dharynka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/tapia_dharynka/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dharynka Tapia is currently a fourth-year undergraduate student pursuing Statistics &amp;amp; Data Science and Economics degrees at UC Santa Barbara. 
She is a Student Engagement and Enrichment in Data Science (SEEDS) Undergraduate Research Fellow, and is interested in machine learning, artificial intelligence, and computer vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she is not studying, she enjoys trying new places to eat with friends. She has also been working for the Santa Barbara School District as a high school math tutor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/teshome_eyob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/teshome_eyob/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Eyob is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. He is a Student Engagement and Enrichment in Data Science (SEEDS) Undergraduate Research Fellow, and is interested in Artificial Intelligence, Virtual Reality, and Computer Vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he is not in class or studying in the library, he enjoys working out, hanging out with friends, and playing soccer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/tharanipathy_archita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/tharanipathy_archita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Archita Tharanipathy is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Biochemistry and Molecular Biology degree at the University of California, Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/turkstra_lily2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/turkstra_lily2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lily Turkstra&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/vahid_amirali/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/vahid_amirali/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Amirali Vahid is a Postdoctoral Researcher at UC Santa Barbara.
He received his PhD in Psychology from Technische Universität Dresden, Germany, as well as a BS and MS in Electrical Engineering from the University of Tehran, Iran.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is interested in applying machine learning models and computer vision to biological and biomedical applications.
In particular, his research focuses on determining how the mouse brain extracts relevant visual features from the rich, dynamic visual input that typifies active exploration, and to investigate how the neural representations of these features can support visual navigation.
For this, he is performing data-driven statistical analyses and developing (deep) predictive models of brain activity based on visual input and several behavioral variables.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/vanos_lexie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/vanos_lexie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lexie Van Os is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences and Communication degrees at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested cognitive neuroscience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/varesio_wade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/varesio_wade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wade Varesio is currently a fourth-year undergraduate student in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/wei_francie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/wei_francie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Francie Wei is currently a fourth-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in machine learning behind artificial vision.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/wu_nathan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/wu_nathan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nathan Wu is an undergraduate research assistant in the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is a fourth-year undergraduate student in Computer Science as well as in Statistics and Data Science at UCSB. In the Bionic Vision Lab, he works on projects seeking to improve AR/VR for people with low vision.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/yan_kelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/yan_kelly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kelly Yan is an undergraduate research assistant in the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/ye_zhongyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/ye_zhongyi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/yoffe_luke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/yoffe_luke/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Luke Yoffe is currently in his third and final year of undergraduate studies in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara.  He is interested in Machine Learning and Software Engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his free time, Luke enjoys playing soccer, playing video games, and going on walks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/zhong_wanqian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/alumni/zhong_wanqian/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daisy Zhong is a second-year undergraduate studying Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in human-computer interaction, software, and psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Daisy enjoys hiking, baking, and hanging out with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
