<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lab Members on Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lab Members on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/adimulam_kartik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/adimulam_kartik/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kartik Adimulam is a 3rd-year undergraduate Statistics &amp;amp; Data Science major at UC Santa Barbara. He is fascinated by the use of artificial intelligence and computational neuroscience to solve modern-day health issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he is not learning about data science or pursuing his interests as a researcher, he enjoys watching podcasts and playing basketball with his fraternity. He also enjoys working on supplementary personal data science projects focused on algorithmic trading.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/aguilar_fatima/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/aguilar_fatima/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fatima Aguilar is an undergraduate student pursuing English and Sociology degrees at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/arora_kanav/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/arora_kanav/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kanav Arora is currently an undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/carter_anissa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/carter_anissa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anissa Carter is a Promise Scholar and second-year student in the Department of Computer Science.
She is interested in applying computer science to the furtherment of the medical field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her spare time, she loves to swim, bike, and hike.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/chou_juliana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/chou_juliana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Juliana Chou is currently a fourth-year student pursuing a Biopsychology degree at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in learning more about neuroprosthetics and deep learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She also serves as a mentor in UCSB&amp;rsquo;s Undergraduate Mentorship Program and is a research assistant in the Keiflin Lab, investigating neural networks implicated in context-based decision making.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time she enjoys trying out new recipes and watching sunsets with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/chung_yongtak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/chung_yongtak/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yongtak (Dylan) Chung is an undergraduate student pursuing a degree in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is interested in the field of natural language processing and is particularly intrigued by the Transformer architecture. In his free time he likes to work on side projects, weight lift, and conduct research on what his favorite TV show is.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/ding_edward/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/ding_edward/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Edward Ding is currently a second year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Engineering degree at UC Santa Barbara. He is interested in the world of computer vision, control systems, robotics engineering and machine learning. He is especially intrigued by the relation of those subjects to computer architecture and hardware design.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Edward also currently serves as an Undergraduate Learning Assistant (ULA) for the Computer Science Department&amp;rsquo;s introductory CMPSC 16 class, tutoring and mentoring first year CS and CE students.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/gangaswamy_harshita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/gangaswamy_harshita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Harshita Gangaswamy is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Engineering degree at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in deep learning and computational neuroscience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she is not studying and doing research, she enjoys reading novels and watching TV shows with her roommates and friends. She has also been volunteering to teach kids through the Society of Women Engineers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/gil_nadolskis_lucas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/gil_nadolskis_lucas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lucas Gil Nadolskis is currently a Graduate Student Researcher in the Bionic Vision Lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucas got his BS in Computer Science with a minor in Neuroscience from the University of Minnesota in 2021, where he performed research related to autonomous navigation, computer vision and brain-computer interfaces. Later, he got his MS in Biomedical Engineering from Carnegie Mellon University, where his primary work focused on analyzing top-down pathways of the visual system and how this could be integrated into cortical implants for the blind. In addition, he worked with the Human-Computer Interaction department on issues related to accessibility in data visualization, an area that he still seeks to explore in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting Fall &amp;lsquo;23, Lucas will be a PhD student in the Interdepartmental Graduate Program in Dynamical Neuroscience (DYNS) at UC Santa Barbara, where he will investigate novel ways to approach cortical implants for the blind. Being blind himself since the age of five, Lucas&amp;rsquo; interests are broad, ranging from neuroscience to accessibility, but can be summarized as efforts to improve the lives of blind people around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside of the lab, most of his free time is occupied by music, traveling and searching for audio-described content.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/gonzalez_isabella/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/gonzalez_isabella/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Isabella Gonzalez is currently a fourth-year undergraduate student pursuing a Biopsychology degree at UC Santa Barbara with a minor in Spanish. She is interested in low vision and neuroprosthetics. Isabella will pursue a career in the medical field and is especially passionate about providing healthcare to underserved populations. She currently is part of a medical brigade club at UCSB and volunteers at the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Isabella enjoys yoga, ballet, and pottery.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/granley_jacob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/granley_jacob/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jacob Granley is a PhD student in the Department of Computer Science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining UCSB, he received his Masters and Bachelors in Computer Science from Colorado School of Mines. He is pursuing his PhD under Dr. Beyeler as part of the Bionic Vision lab, where he hopes to use Computer Science and Machine Learning methods to help improve artificial vision technologies with the ultimate goal of restoring sight to the blind.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/hoffman_isaac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/hoffman_isaac/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Isaac Hoffman is currently a third-year student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara, with a minor in Speech and Language Technologies.
He is interested in machine learning and creating systems which can enable the use of large-scale deep learning models in various fields outside of computing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/hou_yuchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/hou_yuchen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yuchen Hou is a PhD student in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara.
She is interested in computational neuroscience and machine learning.
Her research goal is to model the dynamics of brain functions by integrating knowledge from computer, cognitive, and neural science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to pursuing her PhD studies, she was an undergraduate research assistant in the Bionic Vision Lab with a BS degree in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, she likes reading fiction books and watching action movies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/johnson_byron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/johnson_byron/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Byron is a PhD student in the Department of Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences. He was born and raised in St. Louis, Missouri. He moved to New York City to study psychology, where he received a BA in Psychology from St. John’s University (2015) and then a MA in Behavioral Neuroscience from Queens College (2017). Byron worked as a Research Operations Manager at a start-up company that develops assistive products for blind and low vision individuals (2017 - 2020).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Byron&amp;rsquo;s main research interest is studying how image processing and psychophysics can be used to understand how low vision conditions affect visual tasks. Specifically, how combining computational models with simulated low vision impairment conditions can help inform and enhance individualized vision capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Byron is supervised by Dr. Michael Beyeler in the Bionic Vision Lab and Dr. Miguel Eckstein in the Vision and Image Understanding Lab.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/khachatryan_mari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/khachatryan_mari/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mari Khachatryan is an undergraduate student pursuing a Biopsychology degree at UC Santa Barbara. 
She is interested in visual neuroscience especially the neural networks behind eye surgeries such as LASIK, Photorefractive keratectomy, and lens replacement surgery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Mari likes to jog to Sands beach, try out new restaurants, and hang out with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/kunapuli_sangita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/kunapuli_sangita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sangita Kunapuli is a fourth-year undergraduate student studying Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara. She is passionate about applications of computer vision, deep learning, and using technology for good. Previously, Sangita contributed to the Where’s the Bear project with UCSB RACELab as part of the Early Research Scholars Program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Sangita enjoys singing a cappella with her team UCSB Ravaani, going to the gym, and journaling with a cup of tea.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/levier_tori/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/levier_tori/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tori LeVier is a fourth-year undergraduate pursuing a B.S. in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences at UC Santa Barbara and lab manager in the Bionic Vision Lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tori is interested at the intersection of social cognitive neuroscience, perception, and assistive technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside of managing the lab, she is an RA with the LEAP Neuro lab (Lapate), where she is investigating the temporal coding of dynamic emotional experiences using behavioral and electrophysiological methods. She also is conducting her honors thesis with Dr. Hongbo Yu where she is investigating the moral standing of blame at a group level. After graduation, she hopes to pursue a PhD in computational or social cognitive neuroscience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Tori enjoys baking and decorating cakes as well as hosting car meets as the president of UCSB’s Gaucho Automotive Society.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/li_luke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/li_luke/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Luke Li is currently an undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/lobko_dariya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/lobko_dariya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dariya (Dasha) Lobko is working towards a Biopsychology B.S. at UC Santa Barbara, graduating in 2024. Apart from her work in the Bionic Vision Lab, she also enjoys working as a research assistant in Dr. Miguel Eckstein&amp;rsquo;s Vision and Image Understanding (VIU) lab, where she assists graduate students in conducting psychophysical experiments. Dasha was extensively involved in investigating how imaging modulations can aid radiologists in diagnosing medical conditions (such as breast cancer) in visual search tasks, as part of Devi Klein&amp;rsquo;s project (PhD candidate).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dasha was born and raised in Donetsk, Ukraine prior to moving to Santa Barbara in 2015. She works as a part time medical assistant in a neurology and neurosurgery clinic and has a special interest in patients experiencing neurovisual deficits. In her free time, Dasha enjoys staying active, volunteering at the hospital and helping humanitarian efforts in Ukraine through a local nonprofit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/lu_xiankun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/lu_xiankun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Xiankun Lu is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Physics degree at UC Santa Barbara. Before joining the lab, he worked as a Data Scientist in the High-Energy Physics research lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside of lab, he enjoys philosophy, piloting, and symphonies. He has also been volunteering with the Physics Circus.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/mahmoud_nancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/mahmoud_nancy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nancy Mahmoud is an undergraduate student pursuing a Biopsychology degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/ondo_megumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/ondo_megumi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Megumi Ondo is an undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/pogoncheff_galen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/pogoncheff_galen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Galen Pogoncheff joined the Bionic Vision Lab in 2022 as a PhD student in the Computer Science department.  Driven to improve the processing of visual stimuli for bionic vision devices, he aims to advance techniques in computer vision using mechanisms inspired by neural processing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining the lab, Galen obtained his B.S. and M.S. in Computer Science from the University of Colorado and subsequently led the research and development of machine learning models for wearable electrophysiology devices at a local startup.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/pullela_laya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/pullela_laya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Laya Pullela is a BS Student in the College of Creative Studies and a member of the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara.
She is interested in applying machine learning and computational biology to medical applications.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/roma_ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/roma_ethan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ethan Roma is currently a fourth-year undergraduate student pursuing a Biopsychology degree in the College of Letters and Science at UC Santa Barbara. He wants to learn more about the behavioral and physiological causes of losses in sensation such as sight, and how technical prosthetics might be enabled/designed to address said losses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his free time, he enjoys making music, skateboarding, and late night drive-thrus with his friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/sardina_callie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/sardina_callie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Callie Sardina is a first year student pursuing a MS in Computer Science at UCSB.
She is interested in machine learning, deep learning, computational vision, and theoretical computer science. 
She is passionate about employing computer science within the realm of medical sciences to help make a positive impact on people&amp;rsquo;s well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, you&amp;rsquo;ll find Callie painting, watching sunsets, and doing gymnastics.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/schoinas_eirini/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/schoinas_eirini/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Eirini Schoinas is currently a first-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computing degree in the College of Creative Studies at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in human-computer interaction and new ways for computers to interface with the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, she enjoys reading science fiction and fantasy novels and making art.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/sista_shivani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/sista_shivani/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shivani Sista is currently a second-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara, and a scholar in the Early Research Scholars Program (ERSP). She is interested in deep learning, computer vision, and computational neuroscience. In her free time, she enjoys playing the violin, drawing, and watching TV.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/spiker_madori/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/spiker_madori/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Madori Spiker is a MS student in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/su_jiaxin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/su_jiaxin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jiaxin Su is an undergraduate student pursuing degrees in Data Science and Statistics as well as in Mathematics at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She is interested in working at the intersection of biostatistics and psychology. In her free time, she enjoys running and playing frisbee.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/teshome_eyob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/teshome_eyob/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Eyob is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. He is a Student Engagement and Enrichment in Data Science (SEEDS) Undergraduate Research Fellow, and is interested in Artificial Intelligence, Virtual Reality, and Computer Vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he is not in class or studying in the library, he enjoys working out, hanging out with friends, and playing soccer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/toor_sukhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/toor_sukhi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sukhi Toor is currently a fourth-year student pursuing a Biopsychology degree at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in psychopharmacology and visual neuroscience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/turkstra_lily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/turkstra_lily/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lily Turkstra is a PhD student in the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She has extensive research experience with human psychophysics, has worked with clinical populations, and is well versed in statistical software analysis and programming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before joining the PBS department as a graduate student, Lily served as lab manager from Fall &amp;lsquo;22 to Summer &amp;lsquo;23.
Before that, she was a Behavioral Health and Performance Intern at NASA and a Software Quality Assurance specialist at Tapestry Solutions. She also worked as a member of the Multisensory Perception Lab at Cal Poly and as a children’s behavioral therapist with California PsychCare.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/varshney_apurv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/varshney_apurv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apurv Varshney is currently a first-year PhD student pursuing a PhD in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara. He is interested in improving Bionic Vision using Computer vision and human computer interaction (HCI) techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his free time he enjoys hiking and playing tennis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/wang_alvin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/wang_alvin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alvin Wang is a second year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. He is especially interested in the fields of machine learning, computer vision, and artificial intelligence regulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his free time, he enjoys cooking and playing basketball as well as hiking the numerous breathtaking trails Santa Barbara has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/xu_aiwen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/xu_aiwen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aiwen Xu is a PhD student in Computer Science. Prior to UC Santa Barbara, she received a BS in Computer Science and a BS in Mathematics from New York University Shanghai. She hopes to utilize mathematical modeling and machine learning techniques to improve bionic vision.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/zhao_kyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/zhao_kyle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kyle Zhao is an undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. He is interested in pursuing the fields of machine learning and computer vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside of class, he enjoys swimming, designing origami,  and watching rocket launches.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/zhong_wanqian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/zhong_wanqian/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daisy Zhong is a second-year undergraduate studying Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in human-computer interaction, software, and psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Daisy enjoys hiking, baking, and hanging out with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/zhu_jennifer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/zhu_jennifer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jennifer Zhu is an undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
