<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lab Members on Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lab Members on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/arora_kanav/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/arora_kanav/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kanav Arora is currently an undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/carter_anissa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/carter_anissa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anissa Carter is a Promise Scholar and second-year student in the Department of Computer Science.
She is interested in applying computer science to the furtherment of the medical field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her spare time, she loves to swim, bike, and hike.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/granley_jacob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/granley_jacob/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jacob Granley is a PhD student in the Department of Computer Science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining UCSB, he received his Masters and Bachelors in Computer Science from Colorado School of Mines. He is pursuing his PhD under Dr. Beyeler as part of the Bionic Vision lab, where he hopes to use Computer Science and Machine Learning methods to help improve artificial vision technologies with the ultimate goal of restoring sight to the blind.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/hou_yuchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/hou_yuchen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yuchen Hou is a PhD student in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara.
She is interested in computational neuroscience and machine learning.
Her research goal is to model the dynamics of brain functions by integrating knowledge from computer, cognitive, and neural science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to pursuing her PhD studies, she was an undergraduate research assistant in the Bionic Vision Lab with a BS degree in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, she likes reading fiction books and watching action movies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/johnson_byron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/johnson_byron/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Byron is a PhD student in the Department of Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences. He was born and raised in St. Louis, Missouri. He moved to New York City to study psychology, where he received a BA in Psychology from St. John’s University (2015) and then a MA in Behavioral Neuroscience from Queens College (2017). Byron worked as a Research Operations Manager at a start-up company that develops assistive products for blind and low vision individuals (2017 - 2020).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Byron&amp;rsquo;s main research interest is studying how image processing and psychophysics can be used to understand how low vision conditions affect visual tasks. Specifically, how combining computational models with simulated low vision impairment conditions can help inform and enhance individualized vision capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Byron is supervised by Dr. Michael Beyeler in the Bionic Vision Lab and Dr. Miguel Eckstein in the Vision and Image Understanding Lab.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/kunapuli_sangita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/kunapuli_sangita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sangita Kunapuli is a Computer Science MS student at UCSB as part of the BS/MS combined degree program. Her research interests include applications of computer vision, machine learning algorithms, and augmented reality. She is passionate about harnessing cutting edge technology to help people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Sangita enjoys trying new recipes, going to the gym, and journaling with a cup of tea.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/lapsekili_deniz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/lapsekili_deniz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Deniz Lapsekili is an undergraduate student in Computer Science at UCSB.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is a former IBM engineer, ICPC coder, and research assistant in the Dynamo lab at UCSB.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deniz enjoys music profoundly. He plays several instruments and loves to produce. When he&amp;rsquo;s not grinding in the library, you can see him playing at UCSB parties. He also surfs quite a lot (still very bad at it though).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/nadolskis_lucas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/nadolskis_lucas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lucas Gil Nadolskis is currently a Graduate Student Researcher in the Bionic Vision Lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucas got his BS in Computer Science with a minor in Neuroscience from the University of Minnesota in 2021, where he performed research related to autonomous navigation, computer vision and brain-computer interfaces. Later, he got his MS in Biomedical Engineering from Carnegie Mellon University, where his primary work focused on analyzing top-down pathways of the visual system and how this could be integrated into cortical implants for the blind. In addition, he worked with the Human-Computer Interaction department on issues related to accessibility in data visualization, an area that he still seeks to explore in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting Fall &amp;lsquo;23, Lucas will be a PhD student in the Interdepartmental Graduate Program in Dynamical Neuroscience (DYNS) at UC Santa Barbara, where he will investigate novel ways to approach cortical implants for the blind. Being blind himself since the age of five, Lucas&amp;rsquo; interests are broad, ranging from neuroscience to accessibility, but can be summarized as efforts to improve the lives of blind people around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside of the lab, most of his free time is occupied by music, traveling and searching for audio-described content.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/peng_jing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/peng_jing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jing Peng is a second-year student pursuing a MS in Computer Science at UCSB.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/pogoncheff_galen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/pogoncheff_galen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Galen Pogoncheff joined the Bionic Vision Lab in 2022 as a PhD student in the Computer Science department.  Driven to improve the processing of visual stimuli for bionic vision devices, he aims to advance techniques in computer vision using mechanisms inspired by neural processing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining the lab, Galen obtained his B.S. and M.S. in Computer Science from the University of Colorado and subsequently led the research and development of machine learning models for wearable electrophysiology devices at a local startup.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/rastogi_adyah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/rastogi_adyah/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Adyah Rastogi is currently a third-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. She is working on the HILO project in the lab and is interested in machine learning and NLP, human computer interaction, and data analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adyah grew up in the Bay Area and enjoys exploring nature and walks, going to the gym, and going on fun drives in her free time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/sardina_callie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/sardina_callie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Callie Sardina is a first year student pursuing a MS in Computer Science at UCSB.
She is interested in machine learning, deep learning, computational vision, and theoretical computer science. 
She is passionate about employing computer science within the realm of medical sciences to help make a positive impact on people&amp;rsquo;s well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, you&amp;rsquo;ll find Callie painting, watching sunsets, and doing gymnastics.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/saur_magnolia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/saur_magnolia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Magnolia Saur is a third year undergraduate student pursuing a BS in Electrical Engineering at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in machine learning, computational neuroscience, and deep learning. She is passionate about incorporating electrical engineering within the medical industry, particularly to support disabled and underrepresented communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Magnolia enjoys outdoor activities, crocheting, and caring for her plants&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/schneider_marius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/schneider_marius/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Marius Schneider is an incoming postdoc in the lab.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/schoinas_eirini/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/schoinas_eirini/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Eirini Schoinas is currently a first-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computing degree in the College of Creative Studies at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in human-computer interaction and new ways for computers to interface with the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, she enjoys reading science fiction and fantasy novels and making art.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/stone_hannah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/stone_hannah/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hannah Stone is an incoming PhD student in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/su_jiaxin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/su_jiaxin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jiaxin Su is an undergraduate student pursuing degrees in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences as well as in Data Science and Statistics at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She is interested in working at the intersection of biostatistics and psychology. In her free time, she enjoys running and playing frisbee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting Fall &amp;lsquo;24, Jiaxin will be the lab manager.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/turkstra_lily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/turkstra_lily/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lily Turkstra is a PhD student in the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She has extensive research experience with human psychophysics, has worked with clinical populations, and is well versed in statistical software analysis and programming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before joining the PBS department as a graduate student, Lily served as lab manager from Fall &amp;lsquo;22 to Summer &amp;lsquo;23.
Before that, she was a Behavioral Health and Performance Intern at NASA and a Software Quality Assurance specialist at Tapestry Solutions. She also worked as a member of the Multisensory Perception Lab at Cal Poly and as a children’s behavioral therapist with California PsychCare.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/varshney_apurv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/varshney_apurv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apurv Varshney is currently a first-year PhD student pursuing a PhD in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara. He is interested in improving Bionic Vision using Computer vision and human computer interaction (HCI) techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his free time he enjoys hiking and playing tennis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
