<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lab Members on Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lab Members on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/ahmed_raiyah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/ahmed_raiyah/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Raiyah Ahmed is an undergraduate student at UC Santa Barbara pursuing a dual degree in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences (BS) and Statistics and Data Science (BA). She is interested in using computational neuroscience to bridge the gap between technology and brain sciences. Raiyah would like to apply data analysis techniques to advance brain mapping research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Raiyah enjoys cooking, reading, and going to the beach with her friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/cao_ruyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/cao_ruyi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ruyi Cao is an undergraduate student pursuing a dual BS degree in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences as well as Statistics &amp;amp; Data Science at UC Santa Barbara, with a Minor in Applied Psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ruyi is passionate about computational neuroscience and is dedicated to exploring the brain&amp;rsquo;s complex functions through advanced computational methods. She aims to contribute to understanding neurological processes and enhance mental health treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ruyi enjoys dancing to jazz in her free time and taking short walks along the beach.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/chu_ally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/chu_ally/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ally Chu is pursuing an MS in Computer Science at UCSB through the BS/MS program. Her research explores phase-based image representations in computer vision to improve detection in real-world settings. She&amp;rsquo;s interested in building efficient systems that combine traditional techniques with deep learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Ally enjoys baking, reading, playing tennis, and watching Formula 1 races.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/coe_catrina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/coe_catrina/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Catrina Coe is a third-year undergraduate student at UC Santa Barbara majoring in Biopsychology. She is particularly interested in the intersection of neuroscience, psychology, and technology, focusing on the social perceptions of bionic vision. She&amp;rsquo;s interested in exploring how attitudes toward invasive implants compare to other assistive technologies across different demographics and experiences with visual impairments. She hopes to contribute to a better understanding of the psychological and societal factors that influence the adoption of emerging medical technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond academics, Catrina enjoys thrifting, cooking, and eating good food with great friends. She is also passionate about community service and runs a nonprofit that provides home-cooked meals, dental hygiene kits, and educational resources to underserved communities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/granley_jacob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/granley_jacob/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Starting October 2025, Jacob Granley will be a Postdoctoral Researcher in the Department of Computer Science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining UCSB, he received his Masters and Bachelors in Computer Science from Colorado School of Mines. He pursued his PhD under Dr. Beyeler as part of the Bionic Vision lab, where he uses Computer Science and Machine Learning methods to help improve artificial vision technologies with the ultimate goal of restoring sight to the blind.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/he_yolanda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/he_yolanda/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yolanda He is an undergraduate student in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/herbelin_luke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/herbelin_luke/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Luke Herbelin is an undergraduate student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/hou_yuchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/hou_yuchen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yuchen Hou is a PhD student in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara.
She is interested in computational neuroscience and machine learning.
Her research goal is to model the dynamics of brain functions by integrating knowledge from computer, cognitive, and neural science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to pursuing her PhD studies, she was an undergraduate research assistant in the Bionic Vision Lab with a BS degree in Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, she likes reading fiction books and watching action movies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/joyce_emily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/joyce_emily/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emily is a PhD student in the Dynamical Neuroscience (DYNS) program at UC Santa Barbara and is currently rotating in the Bionic Vision Lab. She previously worked with EM connectomics datasets at Janelia and at the Allen Institute, where she conducted research in cell typing and neural circuitry. During this time, she also developed open-source tools to analyze neuronal morphology and connectivity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emily is interested in the intricate circuitry of visual systems and how its pieces are organized to create the sense of vision. She is also eager to apply insights from animal models to help recreate vision in humans when parts of the circuitry are no longer functioning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/murugesan_srinandha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/murugesan_srinandha/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Srinandha Murugesan is an undergraduate student pursuing a degree in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/nadolskis_lucas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/nadolskis_lucas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lucas Gil Nadolskis is currently a Graduate Student Researcher in the Bionic Vision Lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucas got his BS in Computer Science with a minor in Neuroscience from the University of Minnesota in 2021, where he performed research related to autonomous navigation, computer vision and brain-computer interfaces. Later, he got his MS in Biomedical Engineering from Carnegie Mellon University, where his primary work focused on analyzing top-down pathways of the visual system and how this could be integrated into cortical implants for the blind. In addition, he worked with the Human-Computer Interaction department on issues related to accessibility in data visualization, an area that he still seeks to explore in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucas is currently a PhD student in the Interdepartmental Graduate Program in Dynamical Neuroscience (DYNS) at UC Santa Barbara, where he investigate novel ways to approach cortical implants for the blind. Being blind himself since the age of five, Lucas&#39; interests are broad, ranging from neuroscience to accessibility, but can be summarized as efforts to improve the lives of blind people around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside of the lab, most of his free time is occupied by music, traveling and searching for audio-described content.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/peng_jing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/peng_jing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jing Peng is a second-year student pursuing a MS in Computer Science at UCSB.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/pogoncheff_galen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/pogoncheff_galen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Galen Pogoncheff joined the Bionic Vision Lab in 2022 as a PhD student in the Computer Science department.  Driven to improve the processing of visual stimuli for bionic vision devices, he aims to advance techniques in computer vision using mechanisms inspired by neural processing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining the lab, Galen obtained his B.S. and M.S. in Computer Science from the University of Colorado and subsequently led the research and development of machine learning models for wearable electrophysiology devices at a local startup.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/rastogi_adyah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/rastogi_adyah/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Adyah Rastogi is a BS/MS student pursuing a Computer Science degree at UC Santa Barbara. She is working on the HILO project in the lab and is interested in machine learning and NLP, human computer interaction, and data analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adyah grew up in the Bay Area and enjoys exploring nature and walks, going to the gym, and going on fun drives in her free time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/saur_magnolia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/saur_magnolia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Magnolia Saur is a third year undergraduate student pursuing a BS in Electrical Engineering at UC Santa Barbara. She is interested in machine learning, computational neuroscience, and deep learning. She is passionate about incorporating electrical engineering within the medical industry, particularly to support disabled and underrepresented communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, Magnolia enjoys outdoor activities, crocheting, and caring for her plants&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/schneider_marius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/schneider_marius/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Marius Schneider is a Postdoctoral Researcher at the Institute for Collaborative Biotechnologies. He completed his doctoral research in Systems Neuroscience at the Ernst Strüngmann Institute in Frankfurt, in affiliation with the International Max Planck Research School (IMPRS) for Neural Circuits at the Max Planck Institute for Brain Research. Marius defended his PhD with highest honors at Radboud University Nijmegen in May 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marius’s research aims to uncover how the brain achieves flexible information processing. He focuses on understanding how different cell types and brain regions integrate sensory information to drive behavior. To address these questions, he combines detailed biophysical modeling and state-of-the-art machine learning techniques with large-scale, multi-areal electrophysiological recordings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside the lab, Marius enjoys running, working out at the gym, spending time at the beach, traveling, and listening to music.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/schoinas_eirini/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/schoinas_eirini/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Eirini Schoinas is currently a second-year undergraduate student pursuing a Computing degree in the College of Creative Studies at UC Santa Barbara and has been a member of the Bionic Vision Lab since the Fall of 2023. She is interested in brain-computer interfaces and in using machine learning and data science methods to understand the brain and visual system.  She is fascinated by the limitless possibilities that open up as we better understand how the brain works and how this can change the ways we interact with computers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her free time, she enjoys reading, hiking and making art.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/stone_hannah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/stone_hannah/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hannah Stone is a PhD student in the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara. She previously worked at the Brain Development and Education Lab at Stanford University, where she analyzed the visual processing of text and the flexible effects of task in the human frontal cortex. Prior to that, she worked at the University of Rochester&amp;rsquo;s Marmolab, examining the top-down effects of attention on the oculomotor system and early visual processing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hannah is interested in how biological visual systems respond to artificial inputs, specifically how the visual system processes and consciously interprets these signals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside of the lab, Hannah can be found painting, surfing, and exploring Santa Barbara on her bike.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/thomas_nora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/thomas_nora/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nora Thomas is an undergraduate student pursuing a Biopsychology degree in the Department of Psychological &amp;amp; Brain Sciences at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/turkstra_lily/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/turkstra_lily/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lily Turkstra is a PhD student in the Bionic Vision Lab at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She has extensive research experience with human psychophysics, has worked with clinical populations, and is well versed in statistical software analysis and programming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before joining the PBS department as a graduate student, Lily served as lab manager from Fall &amp;lsquo;22 to Summer &amp;lsquo;23.
Before that, she was a Behavioral Health and Performance Intern at NASA and a Software Quality Assurance specialist at Tapestry Solutions. She also worked as a member of the Multisensory Perception Lab at Cal Poly and as a children’s behavioral therapist with California PsychCare.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/varshney_apurv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/varshney_apurv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apurv Varshney is currently a first-year PhD student pursuing a PhD in Computer Science at UC Santa Barbara. He is interested in improving Bionic Vision using Computer vision and human computer interaction (HCI) techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In his free time he enjoys hiking and playing tennis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/vissapragada_tejas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/people/vissapragada_tejas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tejas Vissapragada is an undergraduate student pursuing Computer Science and Mathematics degrees at UC Santa Barbara.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
