<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>computational neuroscience on Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/tags/computational-neuroscience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in computational neuroscience on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/tags/computational-neuroscience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CS 291I: Bionic Vision</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/teaching/2020-winter-cs291i/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/teaching/2020-winter-cs291i/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What would the world look like with a bionic eye?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This graduate course will introduce students to the multidisciplinary field of bionic vision,
with an emphasis on both the computer science and neuroscience of the field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The course will give an overview of current bionic eye technology designed to restore vision
to people living with incurable blindness.
Students will be exposed to the neuroscience of the human visual system,
key engineering concepts for designing a brain-computer interface,
and computational principles underlying the encoding of a visual scene
into an artificial stimulus that the brain can interpret.
We will cover recent advances in theory and applications,
and discuss outstanding challenges with existing devices.
The course will conclude with a team project giving students the opportunity
to gain hands-on experience of working on open problems in the field
using methods and tools best suited to their scientific background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The course is targeted to a diverse audience spanning from computer science (human factors, computer vision, neural networks) to psychology (vision, psychophysics) and brain sciences (computational neuroscience, neuroengineering).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What would the world look like with a bionic eye?</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/0-visual-modeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/0-visual-modeling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Despite the increasing clinical and commercial use of retinal implants,
the perceptual experience of sight recovery (SR) patients
is surprisingly poorly understood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A common misconception in the field is that each electrode in an array
can be thought of as a ‘pixel’ in an image;
to generate a complex visual experience,
one then simply needs to turn on the right combination of pixels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, almost all SR technologies are likely to suffer
from perceptual distortions and subsequent loss of information
due to interactions between the technology and the underlying neurophysiology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of this project is to characterize these distortions psychophysically,
and to develop a computational model that predicts what a patient should see
for any given input stimulus.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
