<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Low Vision on Bionic Vision Lab</title>
    <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/tags/low-vision/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Low Vision on Bionic Vision Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://bionicvisionlab.org/tags/low-vision/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Information Needs of People Who Are Blind or Visually Impaired</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/information-needs-blind-low-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/information-needs-blind-low-vision/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The goal of this project is to obtain a nuanced understanding of the strategies that people who are blind or visually impaired (BVI) employ to perform different instrumental activities of daily living (iADLs).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Identifying useful and relevant visual cues that could support these iADLs, especially when the task involves some level of scene understanding, orientation, and mobility, will be essential to the success of near-future visual accessibility aids.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simulating Visual Impairment</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/simulated-visual-impairment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/simulated-visual-impairment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How are visual acuity and daily activities affected by visual impairment?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previous studies with people who have retinal degeneration have shown that vision is altered and impaired in the presence of a scotoma. This is also the case when a sighted person is tested under simulated low vision (SLV) conditions. However, the extent to which patient-specific factors affect vision and quality of life is not well understood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Testing sighted participants with SLV allows us to compare performance to real patients, design simulations to be as naturalistic as possible, and assess changes in vision for real life tasks instead of relying on acuity alone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Navigation Under High-Stress Conditions</title>
      <link>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/hight-stress-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bionicvisionlab.org/research/hight-stress-navigation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are known individual differences in both ability to learn the layout of novel environments and flexibility of strategies for navigating known environments.
It is unclear, however, how navigational abilities and situational awareness are impacted by high-stress scenarios and whether augmented reality (AR) could be employed to enhance performance and situational awareness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project will investigate three core questions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How does a person&amp;rsquo;s navigational abilities change in extreme situations?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How can we best train them for these situations?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How can vision augmentation be employed to improve situational awareness?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
